Services

For Business

[Human Transcription

Expert Human Transcription with 99% Accuracy](https://www.rev.com/services/human-transcription)

[AI Transcription

Transcribe Audio and Video to Text with AI Speed](https://www.rev.com/services/ai-transcription)

[Human Captions

Accessible and Compliant Captions for Video Content in English or Spanish](https://www.rev.com/services/closed-captions)

[AI Captions

Increase Global Reach with AI Captions in 37 Languages](https://www.rev.com/services/ai-captions)

[Global Subtitles

Expand Globally with Accurate Subtitles in 17 Languages](https://www.rev.com/services/global-subtitles)

Ignite Your Productivity

Forget meeting fatigue, missed details, and tedious tasks. VoiceHub will change the way you work.

[Newsrooms & Journalists

Capture Every Detail, Break Every Story](https://www.rev.com/solutions/news-broadcast)

[Research & Consulting

Accelerate Research Insights and Publish with Precision](https://www.rev.com/solutions/market-research)

[Legal & Court Reporting

A Trusted Partner From Transcription to Certification](https://www.rev.com/solutions/legal)

[Education

Make Learning Accessible and Boost Classroom Productivity](https://www.rev.com/solutions/education)

[Video Distribution & Accessibility

Unlock New Revenue with Accessible, Platform-Tailored Content](https://www.rev.com/solutions/video-distribution)

[Technology

Fuel Faster Innovation with Accurate ASR Integration](https://www.rev.com/solutions/technology) 

Ignite Your Productivity

Forget meeting fatigue, missed details, and tedious tasks. VoiceHub will change the way you work.

Contact Us

Contact Us

[Give Support a Call

(888) 369-0701  
Available Monday - Friday  
9am - 4pm CT](tel:+18883690701)

[Talk to Sales

Learn about our AI and human-led Speech-to-Text solutions](https://www.rev.com/online-transcription-services/contact-sales)

[Send Support a Message

Have a question?  
We can help!](mailto:support@rev.com)

[Help Center

Visit Rev’s Knowledge Base for Answers to Common Questions](https://support.rev.com/hc/en-us)

back to menu

[Human Transcription

Expert Human Transcription with 99% Accuracy](https://www.rev.com/services/human-transcription)[Human Captions

Accessible and Compliant Captions for Video Content in English or Spanish](https://www.rev.com/services/closed-captions)[Global Subtitles

Expand Globally with Accurate Subtitles in 17 Languages](https://www.rev.com/services/global-subtitles)[AI Transcription

Transcribe Audio and Video to Text with AI Speed](https://www.rev.com/services/ai-transcription)[AI Captions

Increase Global Reach with AI Captions in 38 Languages](https://www.rev.com/services/ai-captions)

Ignite Your Productivity

Forget meeting fatigue, missed details, and tedious tasks. VoiceHub will change the way you work.

back to menu

[Newsrooms & Journalists

Capture Every Detail, Break Every Story](https://www.rev.com/solutions/news-broadcast)[Research & Consulting

Accelerate Research Insights and Publish with Precision](https://www.rev.com/solutions/market-research)[Legal & Court Reporting

A Trusted Partner From Transcription to Certification](https://www.rev.com/solutions/legal)[Video Distribution & Accessibility

Unlock New Revenue with Accessible, Platform-Tailored Content](https://www.rev.com/solutions/video-distribution)[Education

Make Learning Accessible and Boost Classroom Productivity](https://www.rev.com/solutions/education)[Technology

Fuel Faster Innovation with Accurate ASR Integration](https://www.rev.com/solutions/technology) 

Ignite Your Productivity

Forget meeting fatigue, missed details, and tedious tasks. VoiceHub will change the way you work.

back to menu

[Give Support A Call

(888) 369-0701  
Available Monday - Friday  
9am - 4pm CT](tel:+18883690701)[Send Support a Message

Have a question? We can help!](mailto:support@rev.com)[Help Center

Visit Rev’s Knowledge Base for Answers to Common Questions](https://support.rev.com/hc/en-us)[Talk to Sales

Learn about our AI and human-led Speech-to-Text solutions](https://www.rev.com/online-transcription-services/contact-sales)

close

Speech-to-Text Solutions That Fit Any Project

Subscription

Free

For occasional transcription and captioning needs.

Basic

For individuals and small teams with consistent transcription needs.

Pro

RECOMMENDED

For teams and organizations with higher volumes of content.

Enterprise

For organizations that require enterprise security, control, and more.

Transcripts by The Minute

Human Transcription

Our expert transcriptionists turn speech-to-text in 12 hours or less, 99% accuracy guaranteed.

AI Transcription

Transcribe video and audio to text in minutes with AI-powered automatic speech recognition.

Captions by The Minute

Human Captions

Reach a wider audience with human-generated captions in English or Spanish.

AI Captions

Boost your engagement by adding AI generated captions in 38 languages.

Subtitles by The Minute

Global Subtitles

Reach a wider audience and improve search discoverability with human-generated English captions.

Looking for something else?

Rev handles the tedious job of transcripts, captions, and subtitles so you’ll get work done faster. If you haven’t found what you need yet, we still bet we can help.

Privacy Policy  

=================

**This Privacy Policy was last updated on March 8, 2024.**

**‍**Our Policy:
----------------

Rev.com, Inc., together with its subsidiaries and affiliates ("related companies" or, collectively, "Rev," "we," "us," or "our"), provide access to this web site and associated transcription, video caption, translation, and document-related services (the “site” or "services") and may collect certain data of or about you pursuant to these terms. By voluntarily providing us with personal data, you acknowledge that you have read and agree to this Privacy Policy.We may update these terms from time to time as our services evolve and to comply with new and changing privacy laws, and we will notify you of such changes in compliance with applicable laws and our agreement with you.

In addition to this Privacy Policy, your access to and use of this Site is subject to any other agreements in place between us, including our Terms of Service located at: [https://www.rev.com/legal/terms](https://www.rev.com/legal/terms). If you’re under the age of 18, you may only sign up for or use our services with the consent of a parent or guardian.

### Data We Collect

In the course of our relationship with you, we may collect the following types of personal data:

* Identifiers (such as name and email address);
* Commercial information (such as transaction data);
* Internet or other network or device activity (such as browsing history, log data, and information stored in cookies);
* Location information (such as general location information inferred from an IP address);
* Financial data (such as credit card information); and
* Other information that identifies or can be reasonably associated with you

Note that Rev may process personal data that has been collected by our other customers subject to their instructions, contractual requirements, and applicable privacy and data protection laws. In those cases, it is the customer that determines what personal data is collected and how it may be used or shared with third parties such as Rev. If you have questions or concerns about the use of your personal data that has been collected by a Rev customer, please contact that customer directly.

### **How We Collect It**

**Data You Provide to Us.** We collect personal data from you when you voluntarily provide such information, such as when you register for access to the services (for example, your name and mailing address), use certain services, contact us with inquiries, or respond to one of our surveys.

‍**Data Collected by Automatic Means.** When you interact with Rev through the Site or Services, we receive and store certain automatically collected information collected passively via web server logs and cookies.

‍**Data Collected from Third Parties.** We collect personal data from third parties, such as lead generation firms.

### Use of Personal Data

‍**To provide, maintain, and improve our services**, including by analyzing the services and addressing security and business continuity issues. For instance, if you provide personal data to obtain access to the Services, we will use it as needed to provide you with those services and to monitor your use of such services. Also, if you contact us by email, we will use the personal data you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem.

‍**To communicate with you regarding the Services** or to tell you about services we believe will be of interest to you. If we do so, each marketing communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to "opt-out" of receiving future marketing communications. Note however that as user of the Service you cannot opt-out of some administrative communications that are reasonably necessary to the Service, such as billing or service notifications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future marketing communications or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below.

‍**For legal reasons**, including as needed to comply with applicable laws and where we deem disclosure appropriate to protect rights, safety and property (for example, for national security or law enforcement). This includes the protection of our own legal rights and the enforcement of the terms governing use of the services.

‍**Related to a business transaction**, including any merger, acquisition, change in control, or reorganization.

**For other purposes** requested or permitted by you.

If Rev intends on using any personal data in any manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, you will be informed of such anticipated use prior to or at the time at which the personal data is collected, consistent with applicable laws.

### Third Party Disclosures

Rev may disclose your personal data to third parties for any purpose consistent with this Privacy Policy, provided, however, that we will remain responsible for compliance with this Privacy Policy by such third parties.

Rev uses YouTube API Services and Google Calendar API Services to collect authorized data and fulfill services when authorized by you. You can learn more about the associated terms of service and privacy policies via the links below:

* Google: [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy)
* YouTube: [https://www.youtube.com/t/terms](https://www.youtube.com/t/terms)
* YouTube API: [https://developers.google.com/youtube/terms/api-services-terms-of-service](https://developers.google.com/youtube/terms/api-services-terms-of-service)

You can revoke Rev's access to your data from YouTube and Google Calendar via the Google Security settings page here: [https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions](https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions). Note that revoking such authorizations may limit or eliminate certain functionality on Rev.

Our site and services may contain links to other web sites or services not operated or controlled by Rev (the **"**Third-Party Sites**"**). The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to the Third-Party Sites. The links from our Services do not imply that Rev endorses or has reviewed the Third-Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies.

### Data Protection and Retention

Rev is located in the United States, and our related companies and other third parties authorized to receive data under this Privacy Policy are located throughout the world. You acknowledge and agree that any personal data provided to us may be stored in or accessed from multiple countries, including the United States. Whenever we transfer personal information to other jurisdictions, we will ensure that the information is transferred in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable data protection laws.

Rev takes steps to protect personal data from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet, email or other electronic transmission is ever fully secure or error free, so we cannot assure you that your personal data will never be used or disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, and you should take special care in deciding what information you provide to us. We may use de-identified data in some instances; we will not attempt to re-identify such data or, if it ever becomes necessary to do so, we will treat such data as personal data subject to applicable law.

We will retain personal data for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. To provide security and business continuity for the activities described in this Privacy Policy, we make backups of certain data, which we may retain for longer than the original personal data.

### ‍**Your Rights**

In operating our Site, we may also use a technology called "cookies." A cookie is a piece of information that the computer that hosts our Site gives to your browser when you access the Site. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the Site and help us analyze Site usage more accurately. For instance, our Site may set a cookie on your browser that allows you to access the Site without needing to remember and then enter a password more than once during a visit to the Site. You can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information. (e.g., [Internet Explorer](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies); [Microsoft Edge](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/4468242/microsoft-edge-browsing-data-and-privacy-microsoft-privacy); [Google Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en); [Mozilla Firefox](http://kb.mozillazine.org/Cookies#Firefox); or [Apple Safari](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH5042?locale=en_US)).Please note that by blocking any or all cookies, you may not have access to certain features or offerings of the Services.

We may use third-party web analytics services (such as those of Google Analytics) on our Services to collect and analyze the information discussed above, and to engage in auditing, research or reporting. The information (including your IP address) collected by various analytics technologies described in above may be disclosed to or collected directly by these service providers, who use the information to evaluate your use of the Services, including by noting the third-party website from which you arrive, analyzing usage trends, assisting with fraud prevention, providing certain features to you, and other purposes. To prevent Google Analytics from using your information for analytics, you may install the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on by clicking [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). If you receive email from us, we may use certain analytics tools, such as clear GIFs, to capture data such as when you open our message or click on any links or banners our email contains. This data allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our communications and marketing campaigns.

Third parties whose products or services are accessible or marketed via the Services may also place cookies or other tracking technologies on your computer or other device to collect information about your use of the Services, in order to (i) inform, optimize, and serve advertising content based on past visits to our Services and other sites and (ii) report how our advertising content impressions, other uses of advertising services, and interactions with these advertising impressions and services are related to visits to our Services. We also may allow other third parties (e.g., ad networks, servers and platform) to serve tailored advertising to you on the Services or on other websites or in other mobile applications, and to access their own cookies or other tracking technologies on your computer or other device you use to access the Services. We neither have access to, nor does this Privacy Policy does not govern, the use of cookies or other tracking technologies that may be placed by such third parties. If you are interested in more information about tailored browser advertising and how you can generally control cookies from being put on your computer or mobile browser to deliver tailored advertising (i.e., not just for the Services), you may visit the Network Advertising Initiative's Consumer [Opt-Out Link](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/) and/or the Digital Advertising Alliance's [Web Choices Tool](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN) to opt-out of receiving tailored advertising from companies that participate in those programs. Please note that to the extent advertising technology is integrated into the Services, you may still receive advertising content even if you opt out of tailored advertising. In that case, the advertising content will just not be tailored to your interests. Also, we do not control any of the above opt-out links and are not responsible for any choices you make using these mechanisms or the continued availability or accuracy of these mechanisms.

We do not engage in profiling of consumers in furtherance of automated decision-making that produce legal or similarly significant effects as those terms are defined under applicable data privacy laws.

### ‍**For EU, Swiss, and UK Residents**

If you are a resident of the European Union, Switzerland, or the United Kingdom, the additional terms in this Section apply to you and to our collection and use of your personal data.

Note that we process your personal data on one or more of the following legal bases:

* as necessary to enter into a contract with you or a legal entity you represent, to perform our contractual obligations, to provide AWS Offerings, to respond to requests from you, or to provide customer support;
* where we have a legitimate interest, as described in this Privacy Notice (see How We Use Personal Information above);
* as necessary to comply with relevant law and legal obligations, including to respond to lawful requests and orders; or
* with your consent

To keep your personal data accurate, current, and complete, please contact us as specified below. We will take reasonable steps to update or correct personal data in our possession that you have previously submitted via this Site or Services.

The law of your jurisdiction may give you additional rights to request access to and rectification or erasure of certain of your personal data we hold. In some cases, you may be entitled to receive a copy of the personal data you provided to us in portable form or to request that we transmit it to a third party. The law may also give you the right to request restrictions on the processing of your personal data, to object to processing of your personal data, or to withdraw consent for the processing of your personal data (which will not affect the legality of any processing that happened before your request takes effect). You may contact us as described below to make these requests. For example, residents of the European Economic Area and certain other jurisdictions may have a right to opt out of our processing of personal data for direct marketing purposes. You can exercise this right by contacting us as described below. Our marketing emails and certain other communications include unsubscribe instructions, which you can use to limit or stop the relevant communications. Opt-out processes may take some time to complete, consistent with applicable law. Certain communications (such as certain billing-related communications or emergency service messages) are not subject to opt-out.

You may contact us with any concern or complaint regarding our privacy practices, and you also may lodge a complaint with the relevant governmental authority.

### **For California Residents**

This Additional California Privacy Notice applies solely to California residents. It applies to personal information we collect on or through the Services and through other means (such as information collected offline, in person, and over the telephone).

In the preceding twelve months, we or our service providers may have collected the categories of personal information about you (“Data We Collect”) from the sources (“How We Collect It”) and for the purposes (“Use of Personal Data”) each described above.

California law may permit California residents to request that we:

* Provide you the categories of personal information we have collected or disclosed about you in the last twelve months; the categories of sources of such information; the business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling your personal information; and the categories of third parties with whom we shared personal information.
* Provide access to and/or a copy of certain information we hold about you.
* Delete certain information we have about you.

You may have the right to receive information about the financial incentives that we offer to you, if any. You also have the right to not be discriminated against (as provided for in applicable law) for exercising certain of your rights. Certain information (such as information we collect about our employees or job applicants, or information we collect from employees, owners, directors, officers, or contractors of businesses in the course of our provision or receipt of business-related services) may be exempt from such requests under applicable law. We need certain types of information so that we can provide the Services. If you ask us to delete it, you may no longer be able to access or use the Services.

Rev does not sell your personal information as we understand that term to be defined by the California Consumer Privacy Act ("CCPA") and its implementing regulations. However, some people have taken the position that when a website uses third parties' cookies or similar technology for its own analytics or advertising purposes, the website is engaged in a "sale" under the CCPA if the third parties have some ability to use, disclose or retain the data to improve their service or to take steps beyond the most narrowly drawn bounds of merely providing their service to the website/app. Some take this position even when the website pays the third party (not vice versa), and in most cases merely provides the third party with an opportunity to collect data directly, instead of providing personal information to the third party. If you take the position that any of those relationships involve a "sale" within the meaning of the CCPA, then you may consider Rev to have "sold" what the CCPA calls "identifiers" (like IP addresses), "internet or other electronic network activity information" (like information regarding an individual's browsing interactions on the Rev site), and "commercial information" (like the fact that a browser visited a page directed to people who are considering obtaining services from us) to those sorts of companies. While Rev does not believe these are "sales" as that term is defined under the CCPA, you can opt out of this activity by following the directions in the Tailored Online Advertising section above.

If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please submit a request through this form or at support@rev.com. You will be required to verify your identity before we fulfill your request. You can also designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf. To do so, you must provide us with written authorization or a power of attorney, signed by you, for the agent to act on your behalf. You will still need to verify your identity directly with us.

**California Privacy Rights Act Sensitive Personal Information Disclosure**. The categories of data that we collect and disclose for a business purpose include “sensitive personal information” as defined under the California Privacy Rights Act. We do not use or disclose sensitive personal information for any purpose not expressly permitted by the California Privacy Rights Act.

‍**California Privacy Rights Act Retention Disclosure**. We keep your personal information to enable your continued use of the service and for as long as required in order to fulfill the relevant purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.

**California Privacy Rights Act Non-Discrimination Statement**. We will not discriminate against any consumer for exercising their rights under the California Privacy Rights Act.

### For Nevada Residents

Under Nevada law, certain Nevada consumers may opt out of the sale of "personally identifiable information" for monetary consideration to a person for that person to license or sell such information to additional persons. "Personally identifiable information" includes first and last name, address, email address, phone number, Social Security Number, or an identifier that allows a specific person to be contacted either physically or online. We do not engage in such activity; however, if you are a Nevada resident who has purchased or leased goods or services from us, you may submit a request to opt out of any potential future sales under Nevada law by support@rev.com. Please note we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity and the authenticity of the request. Once verified, we will maintain your request in the event our practices change.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our Services, you may contact us as follows:

* By mail: 1717 W 6th St, Ste 310, Austin, TX, 78703
* By phone: 888-369-0701
* By email: [support@rev.com](mailto:support@rev.com)

‍

© rev.com
